[Patrick]
Just think..
...this was once the seabed
of a prehistoric ocean.
[Teresa]
'So?'
So it lends perspective
in the great scheme of things
just how insignificant,
how small, how tiny we are.
Maybe for you.
- Cho, what do we got?
- Tiny.
License and registration
ID him as a Ryan D'Stefano.
Wallet was on him.
No money gone.
Keys in the ignition.
Gas tank was empty.
How'd he die?
Shot from behind
at close range.
Road rage, or paid hit?
[indistinct chattering]
[indistinct radio chatter]
There's two sodas
in the drink holder.
One's diet.
The other's regular.
Body's on
the passenger side
so one can assume there were
two people in the car.
Where'd the other one go?
That's a good question.
Anything else useful?
No, we're still
running down the name.
Found this in his pocket.
[sighs]
It's a start.
[Patrick]
'Hmm.'
[indistinct chattering]
Yeah, I know Ryan D'Stefano.
He worked here for about,
six weeks.
He doesn't work
for you anymore?
Not for the last
six months.
What kind of work was he doing
for you, Mr. Holmes?
Security guard. I run security
here at the casino.
Mr. D'Stefano
is a convicted criminal.
He's served time
for burglary and armed robbery.
You hire ex-cons to work
for security for you often?
No, I don't,
and that's why I fired him.
How'd he get past
the background check?
[Mr. Holmes]
'Look, I can't access
police records as fast as you.'
Once I found out,
I dealt with it.
Yes, you seem like a man
that deals with things.
You got that right.
Did Mr. D'Stefano
form any relationships
while he was working here?
Friends or enemies?
[Mr. Holmes]
'No, he kept pretty much
to himself.'
Can you think of anybody
who may have wanted
to harm Mr. D'Stefano?
No.
We need to talk to your boss.
Where is he?
That would be Mr. Shaw.
He's not here today.
What about any kind of paperwork
you might have on D'Stefano?
Where's that?
This way.
Where's the other guy?
Ah. He does that.
He'll be back later.
This way.
The handcuffs are no longer
on me. They are on you.
[lounge music]
And here's your watch,
good as new.
A round of applause
for our volunteer.
In the lamaseries
of the orient--
Hey, Jack,
where's my 50 bucks?
[indistinct chattering]
From the lamaseries
of the orient..
...to the ancient texts
of Atlantis..
...I have found the key to
controlling the dark energies..
...of the universe.
[instrumental music]
[cape whooshes]
Channeling these energies..
...I would transport
my beautiful assistant
across the stage..
...to reappear in this box.
Seriously, Jack.
I just want what's mine.
'Where's my 50 bucks?'
'50 bucks.'
'Jack, come on.'
Lowlife piker!
I want my scratch!
[Patrick laughing]
Damn it!
Hey, Jack, calm down.
Don't recognize me?
Patrick Jane?
I should have known.
Little heckling,
and you blow a simple pass.
You're losing
your touch, Jack.
Oh!
You ruined my act.
It was good to see you.
[sniffles]
[theme music]
Yeah, I'm doing pretty good
here all around.
This job's just
temporary, really
until the new floor show
at Caesars.
That's next, probably.
Oh, that's great.
Yeah. I'm excited.
I am super excited.
What happened, Jack?
You were headed
for the top.
I still am.
I still am,
[scoffs]
I just, uh..
...I got sidetracked.
I got caught up in some stuff.
I got busted for drugs.
I did some time.
It's not a big deal.
Just, uh..
...just messed with
my bookings a little, so..
That's showbiz. Right?
But I'm working my way
back up, so..
Blah blah blah, that's me.
What you been up to, Patrick?
I work with the police.
CBI.
I'm investigating a murder.
- You're kidding me.
- No. No.
In fact, uh..
[clears throat]
This is my bit. Uh..
...do you
recognize this man?
No, never seen him.
Seriously.
N--y--no, no.
How are you, of all people,
working with the cops?
You didn't hear
what happened?
No. Hear what?
[whispers]
Eh, it's a long story.
I'm here.
Well, I'm sorry I can't be
of more assistance, officer.
Good to see you
so well, Jack.
Yeah, yeah.
Last time I saw you
was 16 years ago
when you opened for me
in Kansas City
and for what it's worth,
you don't look a day older.
Well, thank you,
but you're mistaken, Patrick.
It's you who opened for me.
- Your memory's going.
- Mm. Mentalists.
Big talkers.No skills.
[chuckles]
See you.
Ballistics reports
the slugs came from a .38.
Explains why there were no shell
casings at the crime scene.
We got D'Stefano's prints
all over the car
and on one
of the soda cups.
There's different prints
on the other cup.
Haven't come up with anything
yet, but we're still searching.
If they're in the system,
we'll find 'em.
Okay, what have we learned
about D'Stefano?
Grew up near
the Oregon border.
Brother claimed D'Stefano was
getting his life back on track
since he was released
on parole.
They always say that,
don't they?
All tracks, though,
new town, new job, fresh start
leave all
the bad influences behind.
Getting fired would have
put a dent in that.
What'd he do
after he lost his job?
- Nothing.
- What do you mean, "nothing"?
He didn't get another job?
He didn't go back up north?
Nope, he just hung around in
San Refugio until he was killed.
Here's something.
I called his parole officer.
He said D'Stefano
got into a scuffle
with an unknown individual
at a bar outside San Refugio.
PO gave him a break
and let it slide.
When was that?
Couple months ago,
after he got fired.
Okay, what about the casino?
We finding any connection?
Yeah, owner's a guy
named Nicky Shaw.
He's reputed to be mobbed up,
for what it's worth.
Cho, you and Rigsby
look into D'Stefano's movements
leading up to his murder.
See if you can find anything.
Grace, follow up
on the bar fight.
Will do, boss.
Are you planning on taking
any interest in this case?
I'm looking for clues.
Yes, in the newspaper.
Besides, I heard
every single word.
- Really?
- Yes.
Our victim is either
a hardened criminal
or a tragically misunderstood
Dickensian waif.
Also, the casino may be
connected to the mafia.
Okay, so what
do you think?
"What do I think?"
I think I'm hungry.
[instrumental music]
[country music]
Howdy.
What can I do you for?
I'm curious about a fight
that happened here
a couple months ago,
involving this guy.
That's Ryan. Yeah. They went
at each other pretty good.
You knew Mr. D'Stefano?
What's this about?
He was murdered. You don't
know anything about that?
What happened?
He was shot.
What can you tell me
about him?
You know,
he was a good guy, just..
...hotheaded.
Is that how
the fight started?
Yeah, I mean, after he lost
his job at the casino
he was always going on and on
about getting back at them
so, you know, when the guy
who fired him showed up one day
yeah, Ryan lost it.
Was that Shaw,
the casino owner?
Or the other guy,
head of security?
I don't know. Big black guy
with a shaved head.
Finished eating?
D'Stefano got in a bar fight
with the security guy
from the casino, Dante Holmes.
[Teresa on phone]
'I think we should
talk to him again.'
Oh, interesting.
I'll take care of it.
W-what do you mean?
Where are you?
Uh, be back soon.
We'll talk then.
Sorry about that, Mr. Shaw.
So rumor has it
that you're a made man.
Did you have D'Stefano whacked,
rubbed out, smudged
whatever it is
the phrase you use?
That's funny.
Look, is it an embarrassment
that we hired a convicted felon?
Of course. Does that
implicate us in his death?
Not at all.
Does that make us liable
in any way? I don't think so.
What about the fight
that you had with D'Stefano?
What fight?
He was drunk and angry at me
for canning him.
Can't blame him for that.
So I tuned him up a little.
Saw no reason
to speak about it
seeing as there was no
connection to him getting shot.
Well, that seems
reasonable enough
and who wants
that kind of publicity?
Right.
Look, I run
a nice establishment here.
'Everything is the best.
Next month, I've got'
'an international
poker tournament coming in.'
Top cable coverage.
It's gonna be big.
You didn't know
about the fight?
No.
And you don't mind
that Holmes here
was withholding
that information from you?
- No.
- Hmm.
Look, is there anything else
you'd like to know?
My business is an open book
to law enforcement.
Mm. Mm.
[lounge music]
[applause]
No, I'm fine, thanks.
[instrumental music]
Enjoy the show.
[music continues]
What's up?
We found the gas station where
D'Stefano and his passenger
got gas and sodas.
We got an ID on the passenger.
[Cho]
'Her name's Holly Danvers.'
Paid for the drinks
using a credit card.
Hasn't used it since.
Couple of drug priors.
There's an address there.
Nice work.
Go and get her, but be careful.
If she executed D'Stefano
in cold blood
she's likely
to put up a fight.
Alright. We'll call in,
we get anything.
[instrumental music]
[engine turns off]
[dog barking]
Can I, uh, help you gents?
[Wayne]
CBI.
[Cho]
Do you know a woman
named Holly Danvers?
Sure. We know Holly.
Trailer 60. Fine tenant.
Huh. Her roommate Cheryl's
a pushy one, though.
Complains about
the water pressure.
Is she in her trailer?
No, she went away with a young
fella couple of days ago.
My wife sees everything.
Nobody gets away
with anything around here.
You recognize this man?
Yeah, that's him.
Yeah, I remember because
one of 'em forgot something
and then he went
back to get it.
Can we talk to the roommate?
- I don't think she's in.
- Oh.
I stopped by earlier
to check her propane
but, uh,
she didn't answer.
Any chance we could take
a look around the trailer?
Be a big help to us.
Oh, of course you can.
We run an honest place.
- Go get the keys.
- Yes, ma'am.
Head over.
He'll come meet you.
- Thank you.
[birds chirping]
CBI. We need
to speak to you.
See? Nobody home.
Can you unlock it
for me, please?
Yeah, sure.
[keys jangle]
Stand back.
[door creaks]
Hello?
[fan squeaking]
Your park manager
let us in.
[intense music]
Cheryl? Cheryl?
'Oh, damn it!'
[Jack]
'Prepare yourselves,
ladies and gentlemen'
to be terrified and amazed.
[Survivor's "Eye Of The Tiger"
playing]
Hey. What did you do to me?
I can't feel my toes.
[Patrick laughing]
Where are my toes?
'I can't feel my toes.'
Hey. Hey, hey,
look, look, look.
Her head's in a box,
but she's still talking.
[clapping]
That is crazy.
Crazy.
Holly Danvers is
our number one suspect.
What do we know about her?
Well, according
to her parole records
Holly Danvers did everything
she was supposed to.
She got clean and stayed clean.
Passed all her drug tests,
went to regular counseling
even got a good job
as a waitress
at a place
called Big Frank's.
Big Frank's
outside San Refugio?
Yeah.
That's where D'Stefano
got into his fight.
'They must have met there.'
Love triangle
gone wrong, maybe?
D'stefano and Danvers
hook up, then she catches him
cheating on her with
the roommate kills 'em both.
Does she have
a history of violence?
- No.
- We need to dig deeper.
Van Pelt, go to Big Frank's.
See what you can learn.
Alright.
[sighs]
[bartender]
'Order up!'
Holly? She's one of
my best waitresses. Why?
When was the last time
you spoke with her?
She was supposed
to be working today.
She called in this morning, said
she had to miss a couple shifts.
Order up!
She called in?
What'd she say?
Needed time off
for a personal matter.
Seemed kind of cranky,
so I didn't push.
Like I said,
she's one of my best. Hey!
Hello. Order up.
Thank you.
[Jack]
'I don't know.'
[knock on door]
Hey, Patrick.
What is it?
Well, I caught the show.
It was great. Very smooth.
Uh, the sphinx, nicely played.
Love the Blammo box.
Of course it's all about
the assistant. Patrick.
- Oh, I'm Trish.
- We're old friends.
[whispers]
Oh.
[Jack]
'Yeah.'
Sorry. Uh,
this is Vincent and Skiddy.
They're young magicians
I am mentoring.
[whispers]
Hi.
Jack and I used to work
the carnival circuit together.
Mentoring, huh?
Well, that's great.
Used to be this guy was so tight
he wouldn't tell you the time.
Uh, still owes me 50 bucks
from what, 16 years ago?
I don't remember
this 50 bucks.
Of course you don't.
You know what?
I'm gonna let that slide.
Anyway, I have to run.
Um, it was a great act.
Nice to meet you.
- Be good.
- 'Thanks.'
Hey, uh, I'll call you.
We'll, we'll get together, okay?
- Sure, Jack.
- Alright.
[indistinct chattering]
[intense music]
[door opens]
[cellphone ringing]
Hello, Lisbon.
'You wondering
when I'm coming back?'
No. Not at all.
I wouldn't want to impose.
Whenever you find the time
is okay with me.
Ah. Sarcasm.
Doesn't suit you much at all.
I'm working the case.
In fact, I've almost cracked it.
Really? So have we.
Really? What do you got?
[Teresa on phone]
'It looks to be
a crime of passion.'
'A woman named Holly Danvers
was the last person'
'to see D'Stefano
before his death'
and we found her roommate
dead in their trailer.
Ahh.
[Teresa on phone]
'Yeah, and Danvers
was a waitress'
'at the bar D'Stefano
got in a fight at.'
Ooh. Well, now it seems
to make sense.
Yeah, because I just
explained it to you.
When are you coming back?
[intense music]
We'll talk later, Lisbon.
Thanks.
[Teresa on phone]
'Wait. Jane..'
[intense music]
Security's too tight.
It was 12 minutes, man.
We checked it twice.
Sorry, man.
Gosh, guys.
There's gotta..
There's no way.
We tried, man.
[intense music]
[engine starts]
[tires screeching]
Thanks. Thank you.
[grunts]
Hello, Jack.
[exhales deeply]
Where'd you come from?
I know what's going on.
What are you talking about?
You, you been following me?
The way you fell apart
onstage when I yelled
was the first clue.
Then you lied about
knowing D'Stefano
and now you're palling around
with a couple of ex-cons.
Your friends are more
professional than they look.
I must say that. They did
a good job of casing this place.
What do you mean?
What place?
You're planning
to rob the casino, Jack.
- There's no point in hiding it.
- Shut up.
You can get me
in a lot of trouble
people hear you
talking like that.
Question is, why?
You're not
the casino-robbing type.
I don't know
what you're talking about
and you should
leave it alone.
You're scared.
I knew that from the first
but not for yourself,
for someone you care about.
Cut it out. I mean it.
Walk away.
Holly Danvers
is your girlfriend.
She's been kidnapped
by whoever's making you
rob the casino.
Yes.
But it can't be robbed.
It's impossible.
Really?
I mean,
it's not Fort Knox.
Is it really that hard?
I've been looking at it
every which way.
I can't see
how it can be done
and they've got Holly
and there's nothing
I can do to save her.
Hey, whoa, whoa.
Don't worry.
I can help you.
Okay?
What are you doing?
- Calling the police.
- No, no, no.
They said,
any hint of the cops,
and they'll kill her.
They told me.
Okay.
Then we have to do it
the other way.
What's the other way?
I rob the casino for you.
[instrumental music]
Here's what
they sent me.
You have any idea
who sent it?
No.
But you know how it is.
I meet all kinds of people.
There's some hard cases in
this town. It could be anyone.
Why now?
The first of the month is
when the vault is the fullest
so whoever's doing this
knows how the casino works.
Okay. Well, I'll take a look
around and see what can be done.
Can't be done.
Vince and Skiddy agree
and they've done things
like this before.
And they're doing this out of
the goodness of their heart?
Of course not.
They don't know anything about
the kidnapping or about Holly.
- Nobody can know.
- What about Trish?
She's involved, isn't she?
How much does she know?
Only what Vince
and Skiddy know, nothing more.
Okay.
Well, we'll meet tomorrow
to discuss it more. Um..
and I think we should
introduce me to your team.
[car door opens]
Hey, Jane..
...uh, thanks.
Yeah. Sure.
- Hey. Found something.
- What is it?
Remember Hellion
told Jane and Lisbon
he didn't
know D'Stefano?
- Yeah.
- Take a look at this.
"Master of the dark arts
Jack Hellion performs magic
with the help of
casino employee Ryan D'Stefano."
- You told Lisbon yet?
- No. Just found it.
What's with the flowers?
- They're for Summer.
- Summer? Your CI?
- Yeah.
- Oh. Okay.
Goodnight.
Hey. Nice work on Hellion.
Yeah. Thanks. Goodnight.
Wow.
[instrumental music]
[knock on door]
That goes there..
[Trish]
'Who is it?'
[Vincent]
'It's us.'
- 'Hey, boys.'
- What's this about, Hellion?
You're late. Sit down.
We got a lot of work to do.
what's he doing here?
Jane's coming in
on the job with us.
- 'Oh, yeah?'
- I don't know about that.
How do we know
we can trust this guy?
It's okay. You can trust him.
He's one of us.
Says you. I'm not
doing this with him.
Well, fine. Walk away
from a million bucks.
Tell you the truth,
I didn't think
you really had
the chops for it anyway.
[scoffs]
[instrumental music]
Show us your plan.
Doesn't mean
that we agreed, though.
Lounge, casino floor, vault
'loading dock. Right?'
First order of business,
the lock to the vault.
Okay, it's a
high-security lock
using a combination
of side wards and pins.
I can get into it
but it's gonna take
more time than we got.
Security comes by
every five minutes.
Then we're gonna need a key.
[Skiddy]
Holmes the security chief
carries it on him
at all times.
[Patrick]
I'll take care of that.
The vault, you cased it
yesterday, right?
Yeah. The door in the main room
of the casino
marked authorized
personnel only
accesses both
the backstage area
and a hallway
that leads to the vault.
There's a heavy steel gate,
then the door to the vault.
There's a small window
set into it.
Inside the vault is a bare room with the safe set in the wall.
There's no place
to hide in there.
There's cameras
outside the vault
but we can
put them on a loop.
Nobody'll know the difference. They're not the problem.
The problem
is that the guards
come and check the vault
every five to six minutes.
The safe isn't complex,
but it's still gonna take me
more than six minutes
to crack it.
Okay, so we need to get into
the vault without being seen
we need to return
the key to Holmes
before he realizes it's gone,
then we need to open the safe
without being seen,
take the money, and get away.
Yeah, that's all.
Yeah. Well, if I can
figure out a way to do it
you gotta go along
with what I say.
No questions.
No arguments. Yes?
Yes, absolutely.
You better be on the level.
Or else we got a problem.
Only problem I can foresee
is getting you ready in time.
When are we pulling the job?
Tonight.
- Yeah.
- Let's get to work.
Jane? We need to talk to you.
Well, that sounds ominous.
I need to talk to you as well.
Your friend Jack Hellion
looks good for this.
[chuckles]
You think?
He knew our victim D'Stefano.
And he was dating
Holly Danvers.
We think they were
in it together.
In what?
The murder of Ryan D'Stefano.
Oh.Yes. Uh..
Well, it's a theory.
And you think it's wrong.
Well, I know it's wrong.
I mean, it's way off the mark.
I'm, I'm sorry.
And you know the right story,
of course.
Yes, I do, and I know how
to close this case neatly.
So? Do tell.
I shall, but we're in
a very tricky situation here.
There is a life at stake
and you're gonna
have to bear with me
because what I'm about to say
might sound a little crazy
'but..'
Trust me.
It is the only way.
He said, crazy idea.
- He said, trust me.
- Always a bad sign.
Well, listen,
I'm just a consultant here.
We don't have to
do this all together.
I mean, I can manage
on my own somehow.
Wait.
I will bear with you.
Talk.
[crickets chirping]
[phone beeps]
Uh, it's the kidnappers.
They've given us a location
to drop the money
after the job is done.
Well, tell 'em
we're not doing anything
until we know
that Holly's alive.
[whispers]
Okay.
Oh. They're
sending something.
[gasps]
Oh, my God.
Okay, keep it together, Jack.
We got a job to do here.
You okay?
Text them back.
Tell 'em we'll take the money
to the drop site
just like they said.
[breathing heavily]
Okay?
Okay.
Let's go.
[knock on door]
Hey. Hey, where have you two
been? We go on in four minutes.
We ready?
Uh, there is one small thing.
Uh, those police
that are investigating
D'Stefano's murder
they're here again.
I just wanted you to know so you
don't freak out if you see them.
Oh, crap.
- We gotta call it off.
- No, no. No, we don't.
Everything goes ahead
as planned.
They're working a homicide.
They're not even gonna be
thinking about a robbery.
We do it right
under their noses. Okay?
Okay.
- Let's do this.
- Curtain's up.
[instrumental music]
[applause]
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen.
Tonight I will
delight and amaze you.
[Jack]
'You will see things that will
make you doubt your eyes.'
- You all set?
- Set.
I can't believe
we're doing this.
I'mdoing this.
Well, yeah, but legally,
we're accomplices, so I mean--
Could you shut up?
[applause]
[indistinct chatter]
Hello, Grace. What luck
running into you here.
Hi, Jane. Am I late?
Not at all. Follow me.
My next demonstration
is something I learned
from a yogi mystic
in Dharamshala.
'How to see by using
your astral mind.'
Not your physical senses.
I will need a volunteer.
[crowd murmuring]
You, sir.
[chuckles]
No.
Come on, folks.
Give him a hand.
- He's just shy.
- Go on.
[instrumental music]
I want you to
examine this hood.
It's impossible to see
out of it. Is that not so?
Okay. Uh..
Yes, you can't see out of it.
[Trish]
Thank you.
Please step over here.
[whispers]
Okay. It's coming up.
Can you see?
No. I'm completely blind.
[Trish]
Great, now from our volunteer
could I get an object?
Any object, please.
[indistinct chatter]
Can I have a spot
here, please?
What is the first object
I am showing you?
Is it a wallet?
[crowd]
Ohh!
[applause]
You can go back to your seat.
Thank you.
I will now come out
to the audience.
'Anyone can give me
an object.'
Okay. Hat and glasses.
Dante Holmes.
Like to introduce you
to Grace Van Pelt.
She's an agent at the CBI.
She'd like to ask you
a few questions.
I think you two are
gonna get along famously.
Hi.
So, um...you're
the head of security, huh?
[instrumental music]
Nobody saw you, did they?
Nobody saw us.
You get the key?
Like candy from a baby.
We clear?
[beeps]
Clear.
[dramatic music]
Okay.
All set.
You have roughly
five and a half minutes.
[Patrick]
'Good, good, good.'
Okay, gentlemen, I have to
get this key back to Holmes
before he realizes it's gone.
Wait.
My hands.
What?
I don't think
I can do this.
I'm not cut out
to be a criminal.
Alright.
You're gonna have to get this
key back into Holmes' pocket.
I'll stay here and help.
Right side jacket pocket.
Remember,
right side jacket pocket.
[whispers]
Okay.
Okay, Jack.
Hey, look at this coin.
Look at how bright that is.
Look at the way
the light hits it. Eh?
As you breathe
you will feel your body
slowly relax.
I think you will be able
to tell what I have now.
Is it a pair of glasses?
[applause]
See you soon, I hope.
Yeah, good luck.
Do you have an object,
you'd like to share?
When I click my fingers,
Jack
you will feel
calm and relaxed.
It'll be easy
to open the safe.
When I click my fingers,
Jack
you will open the safe with
great ease...and quickness.
[fingers snapping]
What do you say
we open the safe?
Okay, here we go.
[clicking]
Grace, have you seen Jane?
Um, he was here
a second ago.
- Oh.
- Careful, son.
Excuse me, sir.
Um, which way to the bathroom?
Right over there.
Excuse me, agents.
I've gotta get back to work.
[dramatic music]
[keys jangling]
[clacking]
[knock on door]
You guys ready?
Let's go. You need
to get back to the stage.
Okay. I got the rest of this.
Time to bring the van
round to the loading dock.
Okay.
[applause]
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen.
And for our last demonstration
may I have another object?
I think you will be able
to tell what I have now.
You are holding...a set
of car keys.
[applause]
[instrumental music]
[whooshing]
[applause]
[dramatic music]
[grunting]
Got it.
[door closes]
Okay. Me and Vinnie will follow
right behind you in the car.
- You have the keys?
- 'Yep.'
Alright, we get separated
We meet at the truck stop
at I-90, okay?
Oh, don't worry.
We won't get separated.
- Okay.
- Well done, men.
We did it. Congratulations.
- Okay.
- Nicely done.
Hey. Don't stick around.
CBI's gonna be crawling
all over the place very soon.
Why'd he have to hug me, man?
I hate that.
Who cares, bro?
We're rich.
Open the car. Let's go.
He took the keys.
Bastard took the keys!
That's not the worst of it.
Let me see your hands.
You're under arrest.
[car approaching]
Heads up.
Here they come.
[Holly grunting]
Holly?
- Whoa.
- Stop right there, Jack.
Trish?
Turn around...slowly.
Open the back of the truck.
Trish, what are you doing?
Open it.
Let me see the money.
[Jack]
'The money's in the box.'
Oh, God.
It's gonna be alright, holly.
- 'It's gonna be alright.'
- Yeah, sure it is.
Get over there. Line up. Move.
Trish, you don't
have to do this.
He's right, you know.
You don't have to kill us.
You're right. I don't,
but it's cleaner this way.
Everybody who can identify me
will be dead
and I will be on my way
to Mexico with a boxful of cash.
Drop the gun
and put your hands in the air!
[dramatic music]
Blammo.
Ballistics checks out
for the gun, Trish.
Tell us why you did it
and we'll ask the DA
to take the death penalty
off the table.
What do you mean,
why did I do it?
For the money, of course.
I was robbing a casino.
Okay.
You think I was bitter
because Jack was seeing
some cheap-ass waitress
instead of me?
You're 100% wrong.
Couldn't care less.
It was strictly
about the money.
Okay.
It was D'Stefano that
gave me the idea at first
always yammering on about
getting even with Holmes.
And it was D'Stefano
who grabbed Holly?
- Yes.
- Why did he kill the roommate?
She was in the trailer,
she saw him.
Bad luck for her.
[Grace]
Once he brought you
Holly, you got rid of him.
[Trish]
I couldn't trust him.
He killed that poor,
innocent girl
without a shred of remorse.
Even laughed about it.
No moral compass.
You were about to kill
three innocent people yourself
just a while ago.
And I would have felt
terrible about it.
There's a difference.
You're nuts, lady.
Sign here.
We can never thank you enough.
I owe you big time.
True. Big time.
Plus 50 bucks.
You said
you'd let that slide.
Ah, so you doadmit
that you owe me.
No. Wait, when did I first
incur this debt, anyhow?
You were opening for me in
Kansas City. I think it was '93.
There was a girl,
not as attra--
Opening for you? Please.
Never happened.
What were the drugs
that you got busted for?
You want to get
a cup of coffee?
Because I have a feeling
this could go on for a while.
'Cause whatever they are,
I'm afraid they've undermined
the foundation
of your memory palace.
I'm sorry. I've never seen
Jack like this before.
No need to apologize.
Jane has that effect on people.
[theme music]